

mxnre.github.io



SUMMARY

Hello! This is Ken Suzuki, a fullstack and senior blockchain developer with over 7 years of experience. I love to write code in a high-paced and challenging environment with an emphasis on using best practices to develop high quality software that meets project requirements, budget, and schedule. I enjoy learning new technologies and sharing findings with my colleague

S	K	ı	L	L	S
---	---	---	---	---	---

REACT.JS	\bullet	SMART CONTRACT	••••
VUE.JS	••••	TRON	••••
WEB3.JS	••••	INFURA	••••
ETHER.JS	• • • • •	TRUFFLE	••••
SOLIDITY	• • • •	HARDHAT	••••
RUST	• • • •	METAMAST	••••
PYTHON	• • • •	SOLANA	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Grayblock Jan 2021 - Present

Built a front-end application for minting and staking using React and Web3.js. Contributed to staking contracts with Solidity.

Technologies: DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Escrow Protocol Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

Built a front-end application for minting and staking NFTs using React and Web3.js. Contributed to a contract for NFT registration and redemption with Solidity.

Technologies: DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Centrys, Inc Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

Contributed to one of the biggest mining pools on the AION network. Implemented an IBFT consensus algorithm for the AION Blockchain. Created a permissioned blockchain with the newly implemented consensus. Refactored the core blockchain to allow higher transactions per second. Developed smart contracts for testing new blockchain features.

Technologies: C#, Encryption, AES, Blockchain, Solidity, Ethereum, Java

FULLSTACK ENGINEER

Holidu Feb 2016 - Dec 2018

Integrated Redux and MobX on a number of React-based front-end projects for the better state management of React components.

Technologies: AWS Lambda, GraphQL, Node.js, Vue.js, React, PHP, JavaScript

FRONTEND ENGINEER INTERN

Myxer Mar Feb 2016

Developed a streaming music service front-end that allows users to create custom radio stations Created and optimized AngularJS services, directives, bindings, and event handlers used for radio station user UX.

Technologies: Less, CSS, AngularJS, JavaScript

EDUCATION Bachelor's degree of Computer Science

Nara Institute of Science and Technology Apr 2010 - Oct 2014

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

 \bullet